Muthu vignesh Dharmaraj

Abu Dhabi Emirate, United Arab Emirates

dvvicky92@gmail.com

9500925315

linkedin.com/in/muthu-vigneshdharmaraj-03aa5069

Summary

Automation Lead | 8.3 years of experience | Expert in Ansible, Terraform, Powershell, PHP, Python | Knowledge of developing chatbot, machine learning, PowerBI | DEVOPS | Jenkins | Docker | Kubernetes | AWS | Azure | GCP SQL | Excellent negotiation and problem-solving skills.

Experience



Automation Specialist

Core42

Jul 2023 - Present (8 months)

Infra specialist

Cognizant

Apr 2021 - Oct 2023 (2 years 7 months)

Infra Automation Specialist

HCLTech

Sep 2016 - Mar 2021 (4 years 7 months)

PHP Developer

Webmize

Jul 2014 - Aug 2016 (2 years 2 months)

Working on wordpress project (Theme development, plugin development) and php projects

Education

kamaraj college of engineering and technology

Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Information Technology 2009 - 2013

MNU Jayaraj Nadar Higher Secondary School

HSC, SSLV 2007 - 2009

Skills

Linux • Infrastructure Automation • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Servicenow orchestration • Orchestration • Python (Programming Language) • cicd • PHP, • MySQL • CodeIgniter